# Jorge Andrés Bernal Palacio

WEB DESIGNER

## **Profile**

I'm passionate for digital design and i'm always learning about the latest trends on UI/UX design and web design, always researching about them to improve my process in the creations of designs that make an impact on the users. I have experience in working in a development environment that requires always being attentive to the requirements that the team needs to perform tasks in the best possible way and I'm resourceful when it comes to solving problems that are unknown to me.

## **Employment History**

## Graphic Designer, Neumomed, Medellín

JULY 2018 - JANUARY 2020

Graphic designer that was in charge of the visual part of the project proposed by the company based on Artificial Intelligence as a tool for better care of patients. I did Web Design, Mobile Design (Android), Brand Redesign and Character Creation.

## Web Designer, Branch Development, Medellín

NOVEMBER 2020 - APRIL 2021

In charge of conceptualization, wireframe design and visual design of the websites of the company's clients.

#### Web Designer, Lendflow, Medellín

APRIL 2021 - PRESENT

Analysis and implementation of the best User Experience cases for the creation of demos and prototypes in HTML of the company's software in different web applications to show to potential clients. Design and deployment of landing pages created in Webflow to show to potential clients.

## **Education**

## High School Graduate, Colegio de la Universidad Pontificia Bolivariana, Medellín

JANUARY 2006 - DECEMBER 2011

### Graphic Designer, Universidad Pontificia Bolivariana, Medellín

JULY 2019 - APRIL 2019

Bachelor's degree in Graphic Design with an emphasis on Digital Publications, Illustration and Animation.

## **Details**

Carrera 84 # 35 - 90, Medellín 050032, Colombia +57 3007850600 jorgea.bernalp@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Colombian

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

28 of July 1994 Medellín

## Links

LinkedIn

## **Skills**

Adobe XD

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

HTML/CSS

Webflow

Figma

Sketch

Adobe InDesign

Adobe After Effects

Javascript/Vue.js

## Languages

Spanish

English

#### **Hobbies**

Videogames, Sports and Reading.